jigsawexplorer.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy

## Email Addresses

You may choose to provide your email address to be notified of specific events, such as the release of Jigsaw Explorer [mobile apps](https://www.jigsawexplorer.com/ipad-jigsaw-puzzles/) and the availability of a [white label edition](https://www.jigsawexplorer.com/create-a-jigsaw-puzzle/create-a-jigsaw-puzzle-help/) of Jigsaw Explorer’s puzzle player. Collected email addresses will only be used for the stated notification purpose for which they were provided. We do not share these email addresses with anyone outside of Jigsaw Explorer and SendLoop (unless they were to be requested by law enforcement). [SendLoop](https://sendloop.com/) is the email service which we use to implement our email lists. See the [SendLoop privacy policy](https://sendloop.com/privacy-policy) for more information. If you wish to have your email address removed from our lists then send us an email at .

If you communicate with us by email then your email, including the reply-to email address, will reside in our email storage. The reply-to email address will only be used to reply to email inquiries and will not be shared outside of Jigsaw Explorer and Microsoft (unless they were to be requested by law enforcement). Microsoft will necessarily have access to the reply-to email address because we use Microsoft’s [Office 365](https://www.office.com/) online service to manage our email. See [Microsoft’s privacy statement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement) for more information.

## Cookies

Jigsaw Explorer uses [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/analytics/) to measure its website traffic. Google Analytics stores [cookies](https://simple.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) through the Jigsaw Explorer website as part of its implementation. Note that Google Analytic’s cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. You can find detailed information about Google Analytics’ use of cookies on the [Google Partners](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) page and on the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) page.

Jigsaw Explorer’s web pages contain Facebook “Like” buttons which involve the use of cookies from Facebook. More information on Facebook cookies can be found in [Facebook’s Cookies Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/).

Jigsaw Explorer uses cookies to store your jigsaw puzzle data. This data is primarily used to save puzzle progress so you can return to unfinished puzzles at a later time. The puzzle data cookies do not contain personally identifiable information.

Jigsaw Explorer also uses cookies when displaying advertisements. See the advertisements section further below for more information.

## Error Reports

Occasionally, Jigsaw Explorer’s puzzle player might encounter an error caused by a bug in the browser, in a browser plug-in, or in the puzzle player program itself. In those instances the puzzle program automatically sends error data in the background to the [Errorception](https://errorception.com/) error tracking service. Our Support personnel can then examine the resulting error report and use the information it contains to determine the cause of the error and apply a fix to the puzzle program if needed. The error report contains information such as computer operating system version, browser brand and version, and log information showing the type and code location of the error as well as information regarding the state of the puzzle program leading up to the error. The error reports contain no personally identifiable information.

In the event of an error, the user’s IP address is part of the error data sent to Errorception. The IP address is anonymized by Errorception so that it cannot be used to personally identify the user. The IP address is not stored. For more information see [Errorception’s privacy policy](https://errorception.com/docs/privacy).

## Advertising

The following privacy statement is provided by [AdThrive](https://www.adthrive.com/), our advertising management partner :

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

**For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

**Updated:** March 21, 2019

[Click here](https://optin.sndlp.com/ar0/178/30d13540) to receive email notices whenever this privacy policy is significantly modified.

If you have questions about our privacy policy please contact .
